What makes Black people being involved in local government so important?
Because local government is where the rubber meets the road.
No one is going to ask their state representative, their congressman, even the president, like for anything.
They're going to ask their local council person, older person, mayor.
And that's where everything hits when you think about basic functions, right?
If people's trash can't get picked up, if they can't get their kids to school, if there's no after-school program,
if they don't have access to public transportation, if they don't have internet, all of these things,
most of which are not the responsibility of local government, but that's what they're going to bring to the table
if they don't feel safe in their communities.
And we have to be focused in local government.
And what we have to do as Black people is, one, realize the importance of local government,
but also the importance of understanding where all other levels of government flow into that
and who to hold responsible.